

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Details**

Rawang, Malaysia 012-228 3473 nicholaskhang87@gmail.com

	п	
	•	
SI	•	V.

PHP

Javascript

MySql

HTML & CSS

Java / Ruby / C/C++

NodeJs

**VBA** 

AngularJs

VueJs

ReactJs

Accounting

### Languages

English

Chinese

Malay

## **Profile**

Passionate and self-motivated Software Engineer with set of modern web application development skills. Additionally, I was Accounts Manager with more than 14 years working experience. This might not related to the field, but can be benefits to my personal and soft skills such as communication, team management and planning skills.

# **Employment History**

#### Software Engineer, Pentajeu Sdn Bhd, Petaling Jaya

2019 - 2020

- · Maintenance of in-house application.
- Develop new web application (both frontend and backend).
- · Planning and design application architecture.
- Optimize performance of application and database query.
- Development stacks: Yii2 (PHP), Angularjs, Reactjs, Nodejs, MySQL, Npm, Github, Linux, AWS.

### Software Developer, Xeersoft Sdn Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

2019 - 2019

- · Maintaining ERP core system (web-based) based on clients requirements.
- Debug system errors.
- · System design for new requirements
- Development stacks: HTML, PHP, MySQL, Javascript

#### Accountant, Kuala Lumpur

2005 - 2019

- · Last position: Accounts Manager
- Last Company: Berjaya Hotels & Resorts
- Full set accounts
- · Management team
- · 14 years experience in accounting

# Education

Bachelor's Degree in Technologies (Software Engineer), Wawasan Open University, Kuala Lumpur

2016 - 2020

LCCI Diploma (Accounting), Kolej Bandar, Kuala Lumpur

2003 - 2004

SPM, SMK Menjalara, Kepong

1999 - 2004

## References

Wong Heng from Berjaya Hotels & Resorts 018-220 0161

Loh Kah Jun from Xeersoft Sdn Bhd

016-695 6893